

RAMAN SEERWAN

Senior Graphic Designer

CONTACT



PHONE +964 751 132 0227



ramocreatice@gmail.com



LOCATION Kirkuk, Iraq



BEHANCE be.net/ramocreative

PERSONAL SKILLS

Books, Brand Strategy, Branding, Creativity, Graphic Design, Identity Design, Illustrator, Layout Design, Thinking, Visual Design

LANGUAGE







ABOUT ME

Creative graphic designer with innovative touches and solutions in transforming ideas into visuals. More than 5 years of experience in designing logos, visual identities and social media. Ease of dealing and understanding client ideas. Accuracy in work and attention to detail. The goal is to satisfy clients with projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

The Galaxy Team

Senior Graphic Designer

February 2021 - April 2022 | Saudi Arabia

Freelance Graphic Designer

Senior Graphic Designer

July 2018 - Now | Iraq

EDUCATION

Kirkuk university

Medical student

November 2022 - Now | Iraq

TECHNICHAL SKILLS













